you stop?
Shout It Up.
Let's go! Welcome!
Dreaming On! My
dream...
Dreaming of.
Woah!
Hey, Buggy!
Guess who's back?
Captain Roger's here!
Captain Roger?
It's really them!
And what a flashy entrance, too!
Yeah!
It's Roger!
When Roger returned from Laugh Tale,
Red Taro greeted him
gleefully with a question,
only to break down into
tears moments later.
The birth of the King of the Pirates
caused quite a commotion around the world,
which prompted the Navy
to react aggressively.
The man who achieved
wealth, fame, and power.
That calls you a legend of our time.
The King of the Pirates, Gold Roger.
Except it's Gold D.
Roger Although, being called
King of the Pirates ain't so bad.
It's no wonder the world government
wants to cover up your name.
You've really earned
that reputation of yours.
The world had a name for everything
that Roger gained on the final island.
They called it the legendary
treasure one piece;
they have no idea you do realize
that because of your fame,
everyone is going to be
out to get you, right?
We'll take down Roger! ARGH!
Find him at all costs!
Let's nap his treasure for ourselves!
They say he's got everything
tucked away in his stash!
Looking back now, it's
been a miraculous journey.
Hard to believe how far we made it,
especially with my short life expectancy.
I have nothing but gratitude to you all.
Whoa, whoa! Come on, now!
Where is this jump coming from?
You can't lay it on this thick!
Don't make me blush, Captain.
You rascal!
Then I'll come out and
say it. We're ready.
Just lay it on us.
I am hereby disbanding the Roger Pirates.
The birth is at hand.
Our sovereign shall soon be born.
And another in a distant sea.
And in time the two rulers shall meet.
A joy that even the whales sing of.
We have waited for this
day for far too long.
It's nearly here.
And surely all shall go well this time.
Only ten until the birth.
Then another fifteen to grow.
Who are you?
How are you able to talk so
loudly all the way down here?
So, Charlie, when will this
mermaid princess be born?
This many!
About that voice...
You heard it?
I'm certain it's telling the truth.
Soon a great person will be born,
and one day, it'll even surpass us.
Perhaps we were a bit before our time.
I do wonder who will find
the one piece in the end?
That would be my son, obviously.
You don't have one.
Not yet, but I may have one in the future.
All right, time to drink.
Head us toward some place with no navy.
I'm gonna get off the ship first! Yeah!
Now, listen up!
Be sure that Odin makes
it home safely after me!
By the way, Odin, I plan to meet with
Whitebeard once more before I keel over.
Should I have him send
Izo back to Bono as well?
Nope.
He's gotten quite
comfortable on that ship.
I promise you'll tell him to
take care of White Kashi for me.
All right, will do.
Roger had a few words with Rayleigh.
A man known as the Dark King was
his oldest friend in Confidant.
Then Roger disembarked.
The ship's doctor Crocus sent him off
with a bundle of medicine for treatment.
His disease was in its final stages.
This was a man's farewell.
Not a single tear was shed as
we were filled with solemnness.
Crying wouldn't befit the
king of pirates' crew.
So we stood.
Utterly stoic.
This is unbelievable.
And look at all those
wrecked ships over there.
As expected.
This next part will be
difficult to maneuver.
One wrong turn into a current and
your vessel will be in pieces.
Until this point, we had no reason to
close the country, but that has changed.
We must open its ports to the
world before Joy Boy comes.
You all better take care of
yourselves until next time.
It's not as though I was
the one who was dying,
so we parted ways with
smiles on our faces.
We all knew we would meet again one day.
My dear!
My beloved wife!
I've waited so long for this day!
Hiyori goes!
Chaka!
Momonosuke!
Hiyori!
I missed you two!
Terribly!
I go out to sea for a bit, and as soon
as I come home, you're all grown up!
Yes!
I hope all has been well
while you were away!
My boy has proper manners, too!
Good to have you back, my lord.
You jackass!
Is that how you properly
address your lord?!
I was unaware that you were
deserving of such things.
It's so nice to see you.
Lord Odin, welcome back!
How was your trip?
Otoki, how wonderful!
I didn't expect that
I'd still be so popular.
I neglected our country
for quite some time.
I thought they'd be angrier.
Thank your wife!
This is the result of Lady Toki.
She is a woman of great
character, truly beloved by all.
Every day she would devote herself fully
to helping citizens around the town.
She toiled and sweated by their side,
and told tales of your triumphs,
but never acted haughty
because of her stature.
No surprise the Lady Toki's beloved,
and the people here are quite
fond of your children as well.
Even in your absence, they have spoken
nothing but praise for you as well.
And that's not all.
The number of people who had ill will
towards Jugarra has dwindled down to nothing.
Incredible.
You're all too kind.
My thanks.
Please don't mention it.
We did it out of our love for you.
Right, kids?
I'm jealous!
I wish the ladies liked me!
Hey, Kiku.
I have some news about Izo.
I already heard it all
from Doggy and Kitty.
I'm glad he's well.
Great.
Tell me, what has become
of Denjiro and Ashura?
I didn't see them last year, either.
Ashura became the boss of
the Yakuza and Mountain
Bandits and Kuri to make
sure they don't misbehave.
Denjiro, on the other hand, has
been wandering all over Wano,
borrowing and paying back money.
Neither of those lifestyles
sound very comfortable,
or like they belong in a thriving nation.
Indeed.
There is another reason that everyone
is overjoyed about your return.
I will tell you the
story from the beginning.
After you left, we did our best to run
Kaido in the absence of its daimyo.
However, it was no easy task, even with
the help of the citizens at our side.
I thank you.
It must have been hard.
Tell me, how is my father faring?
I have some unfortunate news. I see.
That would mean he really was
in poor health, I suppose.
What a shame.
I wish I'd been there
for him on his deathbed.
There's a conundrum concerning
the Shogun's successor.
Before passing, Lord Tsukiyaki
made a request that was quite odd.
It involves Odoji.
Please let me money.
The more I heard, the more confused I was.
Suddenly, Orochi was like a brother to me.
All I did was lend him money
out of respect to Yasuie;
that man never once
returned a single coin.
Of it,
either I also learned that
Orochi is a descendant of the
Kurozumi clan that caused a
terrible incident in the past,
so it was even more shocking to
hear that he was occupying the.
position of shogun as my proxy.
Did you notice the factories?
You must have on your way here.
Each is filled with men
who oversee the labor.
They're clear evidence our
country has changed for the worse.
In every region, the workers
are forced to slave away.
Their wages are far too meager to
survive on, all thanks to the shogun.
But how can this be?
Why is the whole country obeying
orders from a lowlife like Orochi?
It's simple.
He has the support of a
despicable pirate named Kaido.
He's a beast in strength
and character alike.
Kaido's the reason why Orochi
can do as he pleases. It's true.
There was one time we tried to
take a step - Not another word,
Kin'emon.
Leave it at that. Tell
me. What is it? Speak up!
Raizo,
Take Lord Momonosuke and Lady Hyori.
out of the room.
Sir,
pardon.
This incident took place
about a half a year ago.
There was a man who refused to work
at a weapons factory and, well...
His family was murdered.
We felt we could no longer stay
passive in the face of such cruelty.
With fury in our hearts
and swords in our hands,
we marched to the capital
to end Orochi's rule.
However we were thwarted, Kaido's
subordinates snuck into Kuri right behind us.
They infiltrated the castle.
Then those rogues threatened
the life of Lord Momonosuke,
future heir of the Kozuki clan
Forgive me
In the end, the enemies were driven
back by Kawamatsu and Dogstorm,
who had been standing guard at the castle
However, it was Lady Toki who
truly saved your son's life
She used her own body to
shield him from a deadly arrow
My sincerest apologies Because
of our reckless actions,
she suffered a terrible leg
injury We put your family's
lives at risk without
thinking first I'm so sorry,
Lord Odin This is unforgivable
Please, show me.
Odin, I'm fine.
The wound has already healed.
Thank you, Toki.
You saved our child.
It must have hurt.
You can't lash out.
I don't want to invite another
attack over something so trivial.
You, you, you call this trivial?
Listen, Toki, I can handle this myself.
You don't know of my past.
I see now how Orochi does things.
Retainers, stay here and guard my family.
Please, Odin.
You must protect Karoo!
While I'm not exactly keen on politics,
I think it's clear what
happened while I was away.
A fool has taken control of Wano.
A weak, cowardly little vermin hid
behind the strength of a fearsome pirate.
and took advantage of a country
where no one could intervene.
I see what he has done.
He's turned this land into a hellscape!
Oh Call backup, huh?
Come in Kozuki Oden is on his way to the
flower capital report to
Shogun Orochi right now
Did you see that?
Lord Odin!
Has he finally returned?
The true heir is back!
Will he become the new Shogun?
Odenshi's land will finally end!
Shogun, you must evacuate!
Excuse me?
And why would I do that?
Kozuki Oden has invaded the castle!
Oden, let's talk!
Don't hurt me!
Careful now!
If you lay one finger on me,
Kaido's not going to like it!
Please think about what will happen
to this country if you kill me!
I will, after I slice you.
Oh no!
I forgot!
This man's crazy!
Orochie!
Please don't do it, no!
What the hell?
Something stands in my way!
A glass shield?
It won't break!
Stop hiding, Orochi!
No, you coward!
Be not afraid of your sake.
I'll protect you.
Hmm.
Have some faith in my
barrier barrier technique.
Anything attempting to breach this
area will be repelled, my lord.
Your strength can do
nothing this time, Odin.
Don't look so shocked.
I thought you would be more familiar with
this sort of thing since you're a pirate.
Have you not witnessed the superhuman
abilities granted by Devil Fruits?
You're a power user? That's correct.
Although in this country
people call it sorcery.
You fool!
If anger and violence were the answer,
your little daimyos would
have killed me already!
It's too late for you!
I'm untouchable!
Face me!
I don't understand how
this farce came to be.
All I know is that my father pushed
for you to be the Shogun's proxy.
But only until my return.
I demand that you surrender
the Shogun's seat immediately.
I never had any intention
of being the man in charge.
However, I can still do better
for this country than you.
Well, that's too bad.
Seems you didn't hear what
Sukiyaki told us before he died.
And what might that be?
Hello.
It's good to have you back, my son.
Impossible.
How are you alive?
Your foolish daimyos were
deceived by the same trick!
It was me!
They fell for this hag in disguise thanks
to the power of the Clone Clone Fruits!
The entire country bought
it for that matter!
They let me take the
Shogun's Throne! Get it?
I have no obligation to
give the position to you!
At this point,
nobody can possibly know what the real
Tsukiyaki was thinking on his deathbed!
Pastor, what did you do to my father?
Did he pass from illness or was it you?
As the crowds looked up at the castle,
cheering for the return of the Kozuki clan,
poisoned arrows rained down on
them, seemingly from nowhere.
Two were injured, spitting up blood.
They both fell blind.
The confused townspeople
could only take shelter.
Suddenly,
they witnessed an enormous dragon appear
in the darkened sky of the capital.
Odin grew from a wild
child to a daimyo of Carol,
then went to sea and journeyed
among the world's greatest pirates.
He returned home many times stronger than
when he disembarked on his adventure.
He was a man thought to be invincible.
Don't you worry, if anyone,
Lord Odin will save our country.
That's him there!
You've returned!
We were waiting for you!
Lord Odin!
The people of Wano saw him as a savior who
could liberate them
from a ruthless tyrant.
Is he okay?
Within hours of his return, Kozugi
Odin stripped down to his loincloth.
Outside of Shogun Orochi's palace.
and danced like a fool.
Orochi and Kaido's
underlings laughed at him.
One, two, three...
The once noble man danced and begged
for spare change, then marched away.
What was supposed to be a momentous
occasion had become a disappointment.
Kozuki Odin, the rightful
heir to the country.
And the man who became their last hope
had turned into a complete laughingstock.
to the entire nation.
And soon, their frustration and
confusion gave way to anger.
The foolish Odin has
hand-takes that amuse.
His fear of snakes has
given him the blues.
And if you laugh with him, you will...
Oden appeared in the capital once a week.
He cambered about in front of
Orichy's castle seeking handouts.
In pouring rain,
gale-force winds
and freezing snow.
We are begging you, Lord Odin.
Tell us the truth.
It's all we ask.
What did you gonna
speak about with Orochi?
Why do this?
You've lost the support of even
your most faithful followers.
Everyone's grown tired of this charade.
I choose to dance in the
buff every week as my job.
That's how I support my family!
Word of his attics in the
capital reached Carol, too.
Oh, don't forget one last thing,
the shirataki noodles, not bad.
Whatever you do when you grow up,
don't be spineless like Lord Odin.
You think real samurai
would act as a lapdog?
They would sooner commit seppuku.
Health is good for you,
better put it in the stew.
Perfect stock and perfect
broth, brewing up for you!
Then, a year later...
Oden read the newspaper he received
from abroad, courtesy of Shogun Orochi.
He ran up and down the coast.
He couldn't help himself from wailing,
then laughing, then wailing again.
Oh, Roger!
24 years before the present day,
the world was abuzz over the execution
of Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates.
The allure of the vast
fortune he left behind
encouraged countless
people to take to the sea,
all of them hoping to traverse the Grand
Line and obtain the legendary treasure,
the One Piece.
This was the beginning
of the Great Pirate Era.
ROAR!
ROGER!
An unbelievable life.
What a remarkable man!
It is now the second year since
Oden has returned from his voyage,
and a mighty clash has broken out in Ringo
between the Gecko Pirates
and the Beast Pirates.
Gecko Moria and Kaido go head-to-head.
While the battle rages
on, a crime is committed.
The grave of Ryuma is
ransacked, and Shusui is taken.
Unfortunately, our hero is preoccupied.
Radish and Frenchhold!
Despite the chaos in his country,
Oden faithfully dances in
the flower capital each week.
I want to play! You're that man.
Perfect chunk and perfect
broth brewing up for you.
Odin wouldn't be Odin.
If it wasn't boiled.
The dullard is in the streets again.
My heart is heavy for the people of Kuri.
The foolish lord, huh?
Hmm, bit of a stretch
to even call him a lord
Stop running, Kiyoti!
No!
It's the way!
I've turned my family into the
laughing stock of the nation
Father!
I love watching you so, so much!
I want to see you do it, too!
Hey, Toki Yes?
Do you wish to leave me?
Are you saying that in jest?
You'd better be.
Odin became known as the foolish
lord of Kuri throughout the country.
The only people still willing to
associate with him were his family,
his retainers, and a
handful of supporters.
Are you certain about this?
You all still wish to
serve as my retainers?
Really think we have someplace
better to be? My lord,
have you forgotten that we've been
acquainted with your naked dancing for years?
No kidding.
This is nothing you know us.
Huh?
Just what do you want
with Boss Hyogoro, huh?
Back it up.
I'd keep a good distance
if I were you. Stop it!
Ouch!
That's not your call to
make. Stand back! As you say.
Sorry, ma 'am.
Greetings, m 'lady.
I apologize for them.
Why not come in and have some tea?
Oh, yo! Odin's here.
That damned auto-chi just
won't leave me alone.
I'd never work for someone like him.
Well, don't put yourself
in danger, all right, yo?
It's funny you stopped by.
I was telling him the other day,
your dancing's gotten so much better.
Stop it, you're making me blush.
Anyway, another cup?
Three years pass.
He's back, still dancing in the streets.
He's certainly devoted to this nonsense.
...instilling it in the freezing cold.
It's getting a bit nippy out here.
Has he no shave?
He is deranged.
How obnoxious. Go away.
Four years pass, and nothing in
the land of Wano has changed.
Then in the fifth year,
Orochi makes a move on Kuri.
It's the Shogun!
What's he doing here?
Shogun.
It's been quite a while, Odin.
Hasn't it?
I found the location for
my next weapons factory.
This'll do just fine.
Oh, Odin, you do great work.
Come on.
Sorgan, a moment.
You're forgetting something.
What about the ship you
and Kaido promised him...
What are you babbling about?
Let's go back to the factory talk.
They need to run effectively, so
I will need the strongest workers.
I'm sure that the people of
Kuri won't disappoint me.
Will they?
Now get to work.
Our country will be the greatest
weapons producer in the world.
Orochi!
I'm back of you!
Aye, yes.
By the way, Hyogoro became a problem.
I had to call in a little help.
Kaido's taking care of him.
It's not like I didn't want
to work with the old man,
but I grew tired of his
countless rejections.
Such a pity he'll wind up dead. Dork!
His underlings did put
up quite a fight, though.
You unhand our boss right now!
It's a shame we had to put them all down.
Oops, they'd have made fine workers.
It's funny thinking back on it, but
even his old lady tried to fend us off.
She might have been a firecracker, but
what did she think she was gonna do?
We shot her dead, of course
No!
I'll do anything!
Don't take him away from me!
You figure the wife of a Yakuza
boss would have more composure
Anyway, how are your kids?
Momonosuke and Hiyori?
Getting big now, aren't they?
They really grow up so fast.
Quite a cute little pair of
children you've raised, I'm sure.
I take good care of them.
I expect to see progress on
that factory when I get back!
That day,
it became clear that the concerns of his
family and retainers were well-founded.
The great samurai had been carrying a
terrible burden all alone for five long years.
Curse you, Orochi, and Kaido.
The time is now.
You have our support.
We've waited years to
hear you say those words.
We'll aim for Kaido's island, wait for
him to drink until he loses consciousness,
and cut off his head!
Now bear witness.
This is the tale of
Kozuki Odin's uprising,
a tale of courage and tragedy
for which all of Wano wept.
With him stood the nine
men he shaped into samurai.
It began at twilight.
The sun was a fierce red as
it warmed the backs of the
loyal heroes marching towards
a long overdue battle.
Even the blades at their waist seemed
eager to settle things once and for all.
They were later honored
with the moniker Akazayo-9,
or Red Scabbards, referring to their
blades painted crimson by the shedding sun.
I can't jump higher than me!
I can't!
Their sole objective was
to slay the mighty Kaido.
But the stirring tale of their
march is but a cherished memory.
For this story ends tragically
with the execution of Kozuki Odin.
The renowned series of events
that are about to unfold will be
told for generations to come and
be known as the Hour of Legends.